<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on ©Prantik Choudhary</title>
    <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on ©Prantik Choudhary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Article I : Dior x Air Jordan 1</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-1/</guid>
      <description>Christian Dior and Nike Air Jordan collaborated together to create one of the most expensive sneaker of all time,the &amp;ldquo;Air Dior 1&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo;.They were officially debuted at the pre fall Miami show in 2020. The low version of these shoes were even advertised by Travis Scott in his Instagram.The high top version of these shoes are limited to only 8,500 pairs and the low tops are limited to 4,700 pairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article II : AMIRI</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-2/</guid>
      <description>Stating the real facts,I have&amp;rsquo;nt been lucky enough yet to get my hands on any of the apparels be it jeans,sneakers,sweatshirts,jackets .etc. made by Amiri but this is amongst one of my favourite apparel brand that I have been following for a long time now. Mike Amiri is the creative director of this amazing clothing line and he made this from scratch,all the initial designs are made by him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article III : KAWS Dissected Companion</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-3/</guid>
      <description>Brian Donnelly is an American artist and designer professionally known as Kaws.The KAWS dissected companion range from a starting price of 1000$ upto a whooping price of 60,000$.These toys are much in demand and generally happen to be out of stock.Kaws has also collaborated with Nike to produce their own lineup of AirJordans. He casted figurative characters and other motifs which were first printed in 2D but were later printed in 3D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article IV : Goyard</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-4/</guid>
      <description>Forget Louis Vuitton,Goyard is the new status symbol for the rich.Goyard bags are nowadays generally made on special orders.The special orders are entirely handmade in Goyard workshops.Goyard has its boutiques located in NYC,London,Milan,San Francisco,Mexico,Dallas,Beverly hills,Tokyo,Shanghai,Hong Kong.etc. Goyard bags and trunks are made from three plant fibres-hemp,linen &amp;amp; cotton.   Goyard&amp;rsquo;s prime press strategy is silence. It forgoes any advertising, e-commerce, and celebrity endorsements,rarely grants any interviews and very occasionally makes products available to the mass market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article V : Cop the Culture</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-5/</guid>
      <description>Following the sneaker culture that is increasing rapidly day by day,here are some sneakers that I feel you should cop under the range of Rs.10,999 in India.The website from where you can probably cop the respective pair(if it does not go out of stock) is also mentioned in the description below the picture along with its price.Before you check them out,keep in mind these are some sneakers that I feel are nice and worth copping,the choice of sneakers may vary from person to person according to their styles and need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article VI : Virgil Abloh</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-6/</guid>
      <description>Born outside of Chicago in Rockford, Illinois (U.S.A.) in 1980, Virgil Abloh is an artist, architect, and fashion designer.After earning a degree in Civil Engineering from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, he obtained a master’s degree in Architecture at the Illinois Institute of Technology. It was there where Abloh was introduced to a curriculum established by Mies van der Rohe, formed from the notions of Bauhaus, that taught him to combine the fields of art, craft and design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article VII : Travis Scott Sneaker Collabs</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-7/</guid>
      <description>Travis Scott could make a compelling case for the most influential man in sneakers right now.While the size, scale or SKUs associated with his name don’t measure up to Mike, LeBron or his mentor Kanye, young La Flame has made sure to deliver the heat over the last few years with a slew of sneaker collabs.Originally signed to Reebok during his mixtape come up, his partnership with the vector did not make for any co-branded releases but did set the foundation for the endorsement work he’d do in the future with Nike, Helmet Lang and of course Jordan Brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article VIII : Takashi Murakami</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-8/</guid>
      <description>Takashi Murakami is a Japanese artist who works in fine art media such as paintings and sculptures.He also produces commercial products such as fashion,merchandise and animation too. Murakami&amp;rsquo;s most expensive sculpture he sold till date at the Sothbye&amp;rsquo;s New York auction bidded for $13,500,000.In 2008, Murakami was named one of Time magazine&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;100 Most Influential People&amp;rdquo;.In September 2010 Murakami became the third contemporary artist, and first Japanese, to exhibit at the Palace of Versailles in France, filling 15 rooms and the park with his sculptures, paintings, a decorative carpet, and lamps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article IX : The Adidas Yeezy Lineup</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-9/</guid>
      <description>Adidas Yeezy is a fashion collaboration between German sportswear company Adidas and American designer, rapper, entrepreneur and personality Kanye West. The collaboration has become notable for its high-end limited edition colorways and general releases offered by the Yeezy Boost sneakers line up. The collaboration has also produced shirts, jackets, track pants, socks, slides, women&amp;rsquo;s shoes and slippers. The first shoe model &amp;ldquo;Boost 750&amp;rdquo;.In 2020, sales for the sneakers reached nearly $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article X : Cop the Culture</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blog/post/article-10/</guid>
      <description>India still lags behind having hyped sneaker stores such as Footlocker,Stadium Goods.etc.Whereas,there are sneaker stores from where you can buy deadstock or reselled shoes in India too but not all sneakers are generally in stock there. People like Anand Ahuja ,Vedant Lamba , Karan Khatri took the first step forward to spread the hype of sneaker culture in India and also opened their respective stores such as VegNonVeg,Mainstreet Marketplace.etc. Yeah,you can say they dont keep the most hyped sneakers but still they have pretty decent collectibles which you can cop to stay updated with the sneaker culture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
